stateregistration.org 2014-11-23

# Texas Vehicle Registration Renewal | StateRegistration.org

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 5, 2014

**We are devoted to maintaining your privacy and are committed to customer satisfaction. This website does not share or distribute your information with any other party beyond the processing of your transaction. Your information is used solely to process your registration renewal.**

We take every precaution and step possible to secure and keep your personal information private. We will not share your information. We will also remove all of your infomation from our records upon your request. To request the removal of your information, send an email to support@stateregistration.org. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy represents the entire agreement with you regarding your privacy and personal information shared with us.

During the processing of your transaction, we may collect information such as your current name, e-mail address, mailing address, vehicle identification number, plate number and state of residence. This information is necessary for registration renewal processing and will be stored for our records for customer support purposes unless you request otherwise. When you provide any personal information to this site, you are providing it exclusively to this site to process your transaction. Your information will not be shared with others for any other reason.

We may use the information collected to process your payment and send you an e-mail confirming your renewal. We may also e-mail you to follow up on your visit to our site. Please note that you may be contacted via e-mail, even if you do not complete the payment process during your visit to this site. In the e-mail you receive from us, you will be presented with an option to unsubscribe from our mailing list. You may also reply to any of our e-mails and request that your personal information be removed from our records.

Please note that none of your sensitive payment information will be stored in our records. This information is securely delivered to a third-party processor through 256-bit SSL encryption, and remains private.

By agreeing to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, you are also agreeing to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service for the state of Texas' official processing portal. You may access the full language of their privacy policy by [clicking this link](http://www.texas.gov/en/about/Pages/privacy-policy.aspx).

If you have any questions about our site policies, you may contact us directly at [support@stateregistration.org.](mailto:%20support@stateregistration.org) Thank you.

_StateRegistration.org is not owned by, nor affiliated with any federal, state, county, or city government._
